A Guide to the John A. Hartford Foundation records, Grants, Series 2 FA1137
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Grants, 2
  - American Jewish Committee: J. Rubin (97-332), 1997 (Box 202, Folder 1475)
  - Teachers College, Columbia University: J. Burton (98-351), 1999 (Box 202, Folder 1476)
  - Turtle Bay Music School: D. Carleton (94-200), 1994-1996 (Box 203, Folder 1477)
  - Turtle Bay Music School: D. Carleton (97-346), 1997-1999 (Box 203, Folder 1478)
  - University Hospitals of Cleveland: C. S. Landefeld (88-277), 1988-1993 (Box 203, Folder 1479-1482)
  - University of Southern California: B. Williams (88-186), 1988-1994 (Box 203, Folder 1483)
  - University of Connecticut: R. Besdine (87-391), 1987-1992 (Box 203, Folder 1484-1485)
  - University of Connecticut: R. Besdine (87-391), 1987-1992 (Box 204, Folder 1486-1487)
  - University of Connecticut: R. Besdine (91-012), 1991-1995 (Box 204, Folder 1488-1490)
  - University of Pennsylvania: A. Pack (87-387), 1987-1992 (Box 204, Folder 1491-1492)
  - University of Pennsylvania: A. Pack (87-387), 1987-1992 (Box 205, Folder 1493-1498)
  - National Chronic Care Consortium: R. Bringewatt (91-050), 1991-1995 (Box 206, Folder 1499-1506)
  - National Chronic Care Consortium: R. Bringewatt (91-050), 1991-1995 (Box 207, Folder 1507-1512)
  - Grantmakers in Aging: B. Greenberg (98-138), 1998-2000 (Box 208, Folder 1513-1514)
  - Grantmakers in Aging: B. Greenberg (99-250), 1999-2001 (Box 208, Folder 1515)
  - Grantmakers in Health: L. LeRoy (99-2049), 1999-2000 (Box 208, Folder 1516-1518)
  - Institute for Advanced Studies in Aging and Geriatric Medicine: W. Ershler (98-221), 1998-2000 (Box 208, Folder 1519-1520)
  - Institutes of Medicine: J. Cassells (93-146), 1993-1995 (Box 209, Folder 1521-1525)
  - New York Regional Association of Grantmakers: D. Nee (89-113), 1986-1990 (Box 209, Folder 1526-1527)
  - New York Regional Association of Grantmakers: D. Nee (89-113), 1986-1990 (Box 210, Folder 1528)
  - New York Regional Association of Grantmakers: D. Nee (90-136), 1990 (Box 210, Folder 1529)
  - New York Regional Association of Grantmakers: H. Simmons (91-132), 1991 (Box 210, Folder 1530)
  - American Institute of Medical Preventics: R. Gordon (no grant number), 1985-1989 (Box 210, Folder 1531-1534)
  - University of Washington: I. Abrass (87-406), 1987-1992 (Box 211, Folder 1535-1539)
  - University of Washington School of Medicine: I. Abrass (91-008), 1991-1995 (Box 211, Folder 1540-1541)
  - Case Western Reserve University School of Medicine: J. Kowal (91-057), 1991-1995 (Box 211, Folder 1542)
  - Case Western Reserve University School of Medicine: J. Kowal (91-057), 1991-1995 (Box 212, Folder 1543-1549)
  - Bowman Gray School of Medicine: W. Hazzard (87-385), 1987-1992 (Box 213, Folder 1550-1553)
  - Bowman Gray School of Medicine: W. Hazzard (91-013), 1991-1995 (Box 213, Folder 1554-1555)
  - Duke University Medical Center: H. Cohen (87-386), 1987-1992 (Box 213, Folder 1556)
  - Duke University Medical Center: H. Cohen (87-386), 1987-1992 (Box 214, Folder 1557-1558)
  - Duke University Medical Center: H. Cohen (91-015), 1991-1994 (Box 214, Folder 1559-1561)
  - National Chronic Care Consortium: D. Paone (96-023), 1996-1999 (Box 214, Folder 1562-1564)
  - National Chronic Care Consortium: D. Paone (96-023), 1996-1999 (Box 215, Folder 1565-1572)
  - National Chronic Care Consortium: D. Paone (96-023), 1996-1999 (Box 216, Folder 1573)
  - National Chronic Care Consortium: R. Bringewatt (91-050), 1991-1995 (Box 216, Folder 1574-1579)
  - National Chronic Care Consortium: R. Bringewatt (91-050), 1991-1995 (Box 217, Folder 1580-1585)
  - National Chronic Care Consortium: R. Bringewatt (91-050), 1991-1995 (Box 218, Folder 1586-1592)
  - National Chronic Care Consortium: R. Bringewatt (91-050), 1991-1995 (Box 219, Folder 1593-1594)
  - National Business Coalition Forum on Health: G. Smith (92-071), 1992-1998 (Box 219, Folder 1595-1600)
  - National Business Coalition Forum on Health: G. Smith (92-071), 1992-1998 (Box 220, Folder 1601-1603)
    - National Business Coalition Forum on Health: G. Smith (92-071) Separated media "A Road Map To Value-Based Healthcare", c. 1994; 2014:023:016; VHS tape (Box 1, Tape AV 11154)
  - National Business Coalition Forum on Health: S. Sullivan/C. Kunkle (95-109), 1995-2000 (Box 220, Folder 1604-1608)
  - National Business Coalition Forum on Health: S. Sullivan/C. Kunkle (95-109), 1995-2000 (Box 221, Folder 1609-1612)
  - National Foundation for Facial Reconstruction: J. P. Hoguet (93-375), 1993-1997 (Box 221, Folder 1613-1614)
  - National Foundation for Facial Reconstruction: J. P. Hoguet (93-375), 1993-1997 (Box 222, Folder 1615)
  - National Foundation for Facial Reconstruction: M. Longaker (97-108), 1997-2001 (Box 222, Folder 1616-1621)
  - New York University Medical Center: C. Cutting (92-240), 1992 (Box 223, Folder 1622)
  - Creative Arts Team, NYU: L. Zimmerman (94-193), 1994-1995 (Box 223, Folder 1623-1624)
  - Creative Arts Team, NYU: L. Zimmerman (97-360), 1997-1998 (Box 223, Folder 1625)
  - Northwestern University: J. Schwartz (97-272), 1997-2001 (Box 223, Folder 1626-1628)
  - People-to-People Health Foundation: J. Iglehart (92-305), 1992-1995 (Box 223, Folder 1629-1630)
  - People-to-People Health Foundation: J. Iglehart (97-246), 1997-1999 (Box 224, Folder 1631-1633)
  - People-to-People Health Foundation: J. Iglehart (99-409), 1999-2000 (Box 224, Folder 1634)
  - Health Affairs (99-336), 1999 (Box 224, Folder 1635)
  - Rampant Lion Foundation: J. Bishop (98-120), 1998 (Box 224, Folder 1636)
  - Spence-Chapin Services: K. Legg (94-297), 1994 (Box 224, Folder 1637)
  - St. John's of Lattingtown: P. Gilbert (98-356), 1998 (Box 224, Folder 1638)
  - Dartmouth Medical School: J. Wasson (92-298), 1992-1995 (Box 224, Folder 1639-1640)
  - Dartmouth Medical School: J. Wasson (96-242), 1996-1998 (Box 225, Folder 1641-1642)
  - French-American Foundation: M. Iovenko (95-184), 1995-1998 (Box 225, Folder 1643-1645)
  - Gateway Rehabilitation Center: K. Ramsey (94-371), 1994-2000 (Box 225, Folder 1646-1649)
  - Gateway Rehabilitation Center: K. Ramsey (94-371), 1994-2000 (Box 226, Folder 1650-1651)
  - Global Kids: C. Nichols (94-338), 1994-1995 (Box 226, Folder 1652)
  - Institute for Health Policy Solutions: R. Curtis (92-070), 1992-1994 (Box 226, Folder 1653-1655)
  - Institute for Health Policy Solutions: R. Curtis (92-070), 1992-1994 (Box 227, Folder 1656-1659)
  - Institute for Health Policy Solutions: R. Curtis (93-270), 1993-1998 (Box 227, Folder 1660-1661)
  - Institute for Health Policy Solutions: R. Curtis (93-270), 1993-1998 (Box 228, Folder 1662-1670)
  - Institute for Health Policy Solutions: R. Curtis (93-270), 1993-1998 (Box 229, Folder 1671-1673)
  - Institute for Health Policy Solutions: R. Curtis (95-036), 1995-2000 (Box 229, Folder 1674-1678)
  - Institute for Health Policy Solutions: R. Curtis (95-036), 1995-2000 (Box 230, Folder 1679-1683)
  - Institute for Health Policy Solutions: R. Curtis (95-036), 1995-2000 (Box 231, Folder 1684-1689)
  - Institute for Health Policy Solutions: R. Curtis (95-036), 1995-2000 (Box 232, Folder 1690-1693)
  - Minnesota Institute for Community Health Information: D. Shaller (93-142), 1993-1995 (Box 232, Folder 1694)
  - St. Louis University: J. Morley (97-259), 1997-2000 (Box 232, Folder 1695)
  - Overlook Hospital: D. Freed (96-244), 1996- (Box 233, Folder 1696-1700)
  - University of California, Los Angeles: L. Breslow (96-123), 1996-1999 (Box 233, Folder 1701-1703)
  - University of California, Los Angeles: L. Breslow (96-123), 1996-1999 (Box 234, Folder 1704)
  - National Business Coalition on Health: S. Sullivan (95-109), 1995-1998 (Box 234, Folder 1705-1711)
  - National Business Coalition on Health: S. Sullivan (95-109), 1995-1998 (Box 235, Folder 1712-1717)
  - Matching Grants Paid, 1980-1981 (Box 235, Folder 1718)
  - Matching Grants Paid, 1983 (Box 236, Folder 1719-1722)
  - Matching Grants Paid, 1984 (Box 236, Folder 1723-1725)
  - Matching Grants Paid, 1984 (Box 237, Folder 1726)
  - The John A. and George L. Hartford Fellowship Program, 1979-1986 (Box 237, Folder 1727-1733)